[
  {
    "Question": "być (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bin",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:39.6685728+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bist",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:18.6390186+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ist",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:35.7028776+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seid",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:47.9219261+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich war",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:41.8526281+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du warst",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:23:49.1267832+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er war",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:37.8551782+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "być (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wart",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:11:02.0056386+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rufe",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:36.9620884+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du rufst",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:35:40.0117951+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ruft",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:56.1065679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ruft",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:31:23.5974053+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rief",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:26.1224882+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du riefst",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:06:19.5834886+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er rief",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:59.6552094+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wołać, krzyczeć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr rieft",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:27:42.6866479+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich singe",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:33:13.0446471+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du singst",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:30.986347+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er singt",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:40:32.9241244+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr singt",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:24.3590534+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sang",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:40:28.3003678+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sangst",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:55:09.6803464+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sang",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:52.5301437+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śpiewać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sangt",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:47:44.305164+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tanze",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:26.8423223+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du tanzt",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:08:51.9905404+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er tanzt",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:46.7861472+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tanzt",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:37:20.8831957+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tanzte",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:41.4900971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du tanztest",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:41:13.8522406+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er tanzte",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:44.7668662+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tańczyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tanztet",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:16.594434+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich liege",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:04.647+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du liegst",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:54.0388679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er liegt",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:58.7591221+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr liegt",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:20:52.8860298+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lag",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:33.1860629+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lagst",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:07:04.1033974+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lag",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:57.8549931+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "leżeć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lagt",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:38.9304347+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich habe",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:14.9619907+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hast",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:49:44.0410276+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hat",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:14.450379+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr habt",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:44.2181233+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hatte",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:29.546222+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hattest",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:05.9624976+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hatte",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:37:40.299163+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hattet",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:29.7348735+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich denke",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:30:45.9336033+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du denkst",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:24:20.1426985+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er denkt",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:03.1619936+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr denkt",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:11.6868674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dachte",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:24.14618+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du dachtest",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:11.098311+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er dachte",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:55.8741387+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myśleć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dachtet",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:50.1988742+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sterbe",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:49.4581095+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stirbst",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:18:13.8649341+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er stirbt",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:50.1700445+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sterbt",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:00.5300403+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich starb",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:54:23.7845913+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du starbst",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:24.4468474+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er starb",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:42:57.7887372+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "umierać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr starbt",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:50:05.0009516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lebe",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:24:26.342661+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lebst",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:14.266234+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lebt",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:12.5503344+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lebt",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:38:54.8494406+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lebte",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:45.5380118+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lebtest",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:00:29.0004536+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lebte",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:59.7782129+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lebtet",
    "ParentId": 33,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:04.9942139+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sehe",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:41:23.3284831+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siehst",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:20:03.68835+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sieht",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:36.3166085+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seht",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:57.2103351+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sah",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:23.3563964+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sahst",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:29.8265668+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sah",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:11.9540786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "widzieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saht",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:48.3830901+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hole",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:05.2822546+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du holst",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:31:27.9733404+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er holt",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:37:56.4897855+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr holt",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:29.7382676+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich holte",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:10:14.8459315+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du holtest",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:28.4232047+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er holte",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:09.5463116+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na h) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr holtet",
    "ParentId": 221,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:33:34.6685981+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lerne",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:33.1269125+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lernst",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:46.9164456+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lernt",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:12.3379974+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lernt",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:21.0631793+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lernte",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:09.5380297+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lerntest",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:02.3033621+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lernte",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:21.2823979+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uczyć się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lerntet",
    "ParentId": 273,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:01.8504159+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraj (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Land",
    "ParentId": 2,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:55.442237+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraj (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Länder",
    "ParentId": 2,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:31.5989826+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świat (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Welt",
    "ParentId": 6,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:10.7832256+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świat (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Welten",
    "ParentId": 6,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:01.2708513+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "człowiek (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Mensch",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:58.8341515+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "człowiek (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Menschen",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:21.5270059+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "droga, ulica (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Straße",
    "ParentId": 14,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:49.1382423+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "droga, ulica (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Straßen",
    "ParentId": 14,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:42.4746289+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ból (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Schmerz",
    "ParentId": 18,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:34.8423636+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ból (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Schmerzen",
    "ParentId": 18,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:05.6710679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ręka (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Hand",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:52:25.5527729+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ręka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Hände",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:08.2504872+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wróbel (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Spatz",
    "ParentId": 26,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:33:28.1485502+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wróbel (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Spatzen",
    "ParentId": 26,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:53.1460868+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rodzic (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Eltern",
    "ParentId": 30,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:32.5341991+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "woda (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Wasser",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:14.9861036+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "alternatywa (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Alternative",
    "ParentId": 38,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:30:39.5096182+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "alternatywa (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Alternativen",
    "ParentId": 38,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:45.4662592+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "numer (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Nummer",
    "ParentId": 42,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:46.3465434+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "numer (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Nummern",
    "ParentId": 42,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:42.3624052+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefon (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Telefon",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:06:26.1915941+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefon (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Telefone",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:06.2419944+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "numer telefonu (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Telefonnummer",
    "ParentId": 50,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:31:33.314907+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "numer telefonu (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Telefonnummern",
    "ParentId": 50,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:04.362551+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "noc (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Nacht",
    "ParentId": 54,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:56.3060683+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "noc (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Nächte",
    "ParentId": 54,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:34.1704535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szkoła (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Schule",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:42:21.7040707+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szkoła (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Schulen",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:52.1866987+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kuchnia (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Küche",
    "ParentId": 62,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:31:18.32424+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kuchnia (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Küchen",
    "ParentId": 62,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:35.3543953+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ojciec (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Vater",
    "ParentId": 66,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:17:06.9374785+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ojciec (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Väter",
    "ParentId": 66,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:21.3861698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stół (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Tisch",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:10:19.7978842+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stół (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Tische",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:17.6420888+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "poranek (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Morgen",
    "ParentId": 74,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:17:50.5304545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "poranek (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Morgen",
    "ParentId": 74,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:12.53056+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gazeta (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Zeitung",
    "ParentId": 78,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:10.1197451+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gazeta (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Zeitungen",
    "ParentId": 78,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:08.4661294+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "matka (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Mutter",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:08.7749623+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "matka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Mütter",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:31:37.7308028+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bułka (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Brötchen",
    "ParentId": 86,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:39.102815+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bułka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Brötchen",
    "ParentId": 86,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:41:43.5891578+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dżem (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Marmelade",
    "ParentId": 90,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:36.9282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dżem (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Marmeladen",
    "ParentId": 90,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:41.6551178+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cynamonowa bułeczka (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Zimtschnecke",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:29:49.9019385+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cynamonowa bułeczka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Zimtschnecken",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:16.9431343+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płatki śniadaniowe (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Müsli",
    "ParentId": 98,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:38.9141852+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mleko (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Milch",
    "ParentId": 102,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:30.0503547+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "banan (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Banane",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:23.1860981+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "banan (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Bananen",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:45.8023282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "plaster, kromka (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Scheibe",
    "ParentId": 110,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:49:33.9494589+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "plaster, kromka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Scheiben",
    "ParentId": 110,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:01.8711108+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chleb (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Brot",
    "ParentId": 114,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:34.244509+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chleb (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Brote",
    "ParentId": 114,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:35.714156+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szynka (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Schinken",
    "ParentId": 118,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:16:03.8497706+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ser (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Käse",
    "ParentId": 122,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:38.4583306+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "masło (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Butter",
    "ParentId": 126,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:09:42.431238+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jabłko (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Apfel",
    "ParentId": 130,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:50.9226438+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jabłko (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Äpfel",
    "ParentId": 130,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:07.6709892+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kiełbasa (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Wurst",
    "ParentId": 134,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:10.5704739+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kiełbasa (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Würste",
    "ParentId": 134,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:05.842488+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "miód (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Honig",
    "ParentId": 138,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:21:33.4400208+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jajko (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Ei",
    "ParentId": 142,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:01.444715+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jajko (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Eier",
    "ParentId": 142,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:42.754134+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kawa (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Kaffee",
    "ParentId": 146,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:23:47.2309492+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "herbata (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Tee",
    "ParentId": 150,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:24:37.9826928+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sok (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Saft",
    "ParentId": 154,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:55.0151482+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sok (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Säfte",
    "ParentId": 154,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:34.4710501+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jogurt (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Joghurt",
    "ParentId": 158,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:42.4183716+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cały (positive)",
    "Answer": "ganz",
    "ParentId": 3,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:10:02.7180034+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szczęśliwy (positive)",
    "Answer": "glücklich",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:32.6741308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szczęśliwy (comparative)",
    "Answer": "glücklicher",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:06.9543959+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szczęśliwy (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am glücklichsten",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:56:08.5041011+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zimny (positive)",
    "Answer": "kalt",
    "ParentId": 11,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:19.8242869+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zimny (comparative)",
    "Answer": "kälter",
    "ParentId": 11,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:11.8283201+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zimny (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am kältesten",
    "ParentId": 11,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:21.1464859+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "młody (positive)",
    "Answer": "jung",
    "ParentId": 15,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:39.6953182+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "młody (comparative)",
    "Answer": "jünger",
    "ParentId": 15,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:21.0264766+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "młody (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am jüngsten",
    "ParentId": 15,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:20.7829467+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "duży (positive)",
    "Answer": "groß",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:53:52.848755+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "duży (comparative)",
    "Answer": "größer",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:18.4262199+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "duży (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am größten",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:20.6581062+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciepły (positive)",
    "Answer": "warm",
    "ParentId": 23,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:51.247107+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciepły (comparative)",
    "Answer": "wärmer",
    "ParentId": 23,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:23:07.2711982+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciepły (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am wärmsten",
    "ParentId": 23,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:02:53.3678786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spokojny (positive)",
    "Answer": "ruhig",
    "ParentId": 27,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:52.6182008+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spokojny (comparative)",
    "Answer": "ruhiger",
    "ParentId": 27,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:26.5225173+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spokojny (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am ruhigsten",
    "ParentId": 27,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:22:29.2646468+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "krótki (positive)",
    "Answer": "kurz",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:11.5764646+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "krótki (comparative)",
    "Answer": "kürzer",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:48.1705082+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "krótki (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am kürzesten",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:44:35.0683423+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich frage",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:18:37.2672256+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fragst",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:18:40.3312615+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fragt",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:01:22.74098+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fragt",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:16:29.0435154+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fragte",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:54:19.5845921+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fragtest",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:02:39.5486066+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fragte",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:17:21.7073845+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pytać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fragtet",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:49:52.1361547+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich antworte",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:16:58.2115802+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du antwortest",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:56.6368277+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er antwortet",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T22:59:28.9169512+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr antwortet",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:57:51.0072941+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich antwortete",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:56:32.143448+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du antwortetest",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T22:58:31.5732226+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er antwortete",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:39:23.3791435+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odpowiadać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr antwortetet",
    "ParentId": 45,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:17:48.41935+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich nehme",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:57:54.9113651+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du nimmst",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:46:31.4105104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er nimmt",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:23:00.1229083+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr nehmt",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:49:09.8802255+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich nahm",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:55:14.4555547+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du nahmst",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:43:37.194725+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er nahm",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:18:47.4672343+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr nahmt",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:47:57.4892166+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schlafe",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:43:44.7868621+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schläfst",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:18:43.9632192+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schläft",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:19:05.3551914+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schlaft",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:17:54.9073599+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schlief",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:52:20.5278573+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schliefst",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:39:11.1311817+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schlief",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:49:58.0090273+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schlieft",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:58:25.3593498+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich will",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T19:50:49.166013+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du willst",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:15:55.5710314+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er will",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:17:25.2913704+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wollt",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T22:58:49.1812751+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wollte",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:23:20.5068635+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wolltest",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:22:34.8267448+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wollte",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:48:49.9282075+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chcieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wolltet",
    "ParentId": 57,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:20:08.8511075+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich muss",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:23:15.1307823+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du musst",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:52:30.7438787+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er muss",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:58:31.7752696+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr müsst",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:46:51.7464094+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich musste",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:56:07.2954882+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du musstest",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:59:59.6951262+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er musste",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:51.5167516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "musieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr musstet",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:22:04.5708828+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kann",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:59.0288021+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kannst",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:54:03.7837358+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kann",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:16:47.9634105+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr könnt",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:48:55.7602063+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich konnte",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:19:49.0990873+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du konntest",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:58:35.4872658+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er konnte",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:43:00.4187798+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "móc, potrafić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr konntet",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:19:53.5631352+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich heiße",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:15:39.8675751+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du heißt",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:46:42.5064127+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er heißt",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:19:17.8991684+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr heißt",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:44:27.4746618+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hieß",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:04:32.43079+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hießt",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:01:36.0368915+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hieß",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:19.3946572+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hießt",
    "ParentId": 69,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:42:34.2908299+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich komme",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:55:18.0716017+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kommst",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:20:12.6510953+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kommt",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:41:57.3468692+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kommt",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:56:45.047461+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kam",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:21:56.0989102+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kamst",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:56:08.9364226+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kam",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:50:48.8420051+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przychodzić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kamt",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T20:22:25.5308538+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wohne",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:50:59.5929011+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wohnst",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:57:26.9043532+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wohnt",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:19.4209821+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wohnt",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:02:10.3679378+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wohnte",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:02:57.5277839+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wohntest",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:07:39.1112887+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wohnte",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:55:49.8484639+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieszkać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wohntet",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T23:59:31.6769798+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich spreche",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:57:32.3123782+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du sprichst",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:10:00.1671704+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er spricht",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:07:28.1675094+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sprecht",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:49:30.2420965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sprach",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:46:50.5533634+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sprachst",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:42:02.5388953+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sprach",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:56:50.6324721+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sp) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr spracht",
    "ParentId": 81,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:29.8769669+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verstehe",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:47:39.5943081+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du verstehst",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:09:33.0872394+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er versteht",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:46:59.3612445+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr versteht",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:01:51.2800203+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verstand",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:52:03.9048169+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du verstandst",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:01:37.6477375+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er verstand",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:34.1512974+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozumieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verstandet",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:38:55.9327622+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bedeute",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:47:05.1144107+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bedeutest",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:55:00.2244747+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bedeutet",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:02:02.1727815+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bedeutet",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:06:51.4955345+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bedeutete",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:50:21.3769614+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bedeutetest",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:36:42.5316698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bedeutete",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:48:28.0101747+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znaczyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bedeutetet",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T22:59:43.564926+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich weiß",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:46:08.2024431+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du weißt",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:02:31.4446745+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er weiß",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:43:24.1147915+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wisst",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:33:24.7006529+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wusste",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:56:44.8884532+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wusstest",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:42:45.9388303+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wusste",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T23:59:26.4930032+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na w) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wusstet",
    "ParentId": 93,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:01:31.8287662+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich mache",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:01:02.2528086+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du machst",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:36.1009184+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er macht",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:50:54.9369102+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr macht",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T23:59:58.044929+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich machte",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:42:37.6027915+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du machtest",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:48.5328006+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er machte",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:07:21.0714436+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na m) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr machtet",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:56:24.3123876+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich brauche",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:44:12.5866691+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du brauchst",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:06:33.959638+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er braucht",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:45:40.9616772+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr braucht",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:46:04.9705073+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich brauchte",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:47:38.0731606+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du brauchtest",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T23:58:39.1971351+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er brauchte",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:06:40.1274395+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "potrzebować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr brauchtet",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:04:36.8146649+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich esse",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:49:26.8980996+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du isst",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:01:25.4528139+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er isst",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:09:18.6232514+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr esst",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T00:00:38.6049419+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich aß",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:46:25.7464375+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du aßest",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:45:54.8824935+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er aß",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:47:52.7451743+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr aßt",
    "ParentId": 105,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:09:55.1272932+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich soll",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:38:25.2513535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du sollst",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:58:04.2163378+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er soll",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:57:22.336345+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sollt",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:58:08.0725464+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sollte",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T21:49:33.1941249+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du solltest",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T20:49:50.4249969+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sollte",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:07:17.31948+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć powinność (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr solltet",
    "ParentId": 109,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:09:14.3192594+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich duze",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:44:53.0089853+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du duzt",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:53:10.6801361+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er duzt",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:49:20.0884515+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr duzt",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:47:40.8646785+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich duzte",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:48:04.0566034+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du duztest",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:20:13.104195+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er duzte",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:51:56.880251+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na du (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr duztet",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:53:00.8642674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sieze",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:49:24.1524308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siezt",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:46:34.112711+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er siezt",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:44:48.5370874+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr siezt",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:53:06.0960807+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich siezte",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:48:49.6086408+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sieztest",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:33.9128276+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er siezte",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:02:18.6554693+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić do kogoś na Sie (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sieztet",
    "ParentId": 117,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:49:42.9844467+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich darf",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:12.7689058+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du darfst",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:22.0168594+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er darf",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:46:11.2327517+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dürft",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:48:32.1686996+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich durfte",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:00.0162417+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du durftest",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:34.0642282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er durfte",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:49:13.0164782+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć pozwolenie (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr durftet",
    "ParentId": 121,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:17.5847581+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wache auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:19.6482424+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wachst auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:43:59.0249137+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wacht auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:48.2161327+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wacht auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:14.8081915+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wachte auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:00.1768528+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wachtest auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:44:32.656882+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wachte auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:55.8481098+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budzić się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wachtet auf",
    "ParentId": 125,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:50.3610088+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stehe auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:09.4161354+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stehst auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:02:10.5114806+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er steht auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:49:29.6564735+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr steht auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:49:37.4165259+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stand auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:45:58.5608258+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du standst auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:26.688187+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stand auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:01:47.2156146+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wstawać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr standet auf",
    "ParentId": 129,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:52:42.6800981+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich frühstücke",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:52:36.3546595+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du frühstückst",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:53:06.6265418+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er frühstückt",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:53:35.0663668+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr frühstückt",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:53:43.5703132+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich frühstückte",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:51:21.9870914+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du frühstücktest",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:50:40.5876286+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er frühstückte",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:53:16.3705035+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jeść śniadanie (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr frühstücktet",
    "ParentId": 133,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:52:20.8987105+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich beginne",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:52:25.0907098+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du beginnst",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:51:25.619191+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er beginnt",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:51:09.5872662+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr beginnt",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:49:57.5318696+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich begann",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:50:30.067457+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du begannst",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:50:45.9393001+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er begann",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:51:13.6672509+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na b) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr begannt",
    "ParentId": 137,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:52:42.9066674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gehe",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:51:04.8031777+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gehst",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:52:02.8829104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er geht",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:53:38.9623304+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr geht",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:51:50.1550538+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ging",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:50:07.2915496+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gingst",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:53:52.5381283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er ging",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T18:55:15.5486619+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gingt",
    "ParentId": 141,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T16:52:12.55482+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sitze",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:38.8825105+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du sitzt",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:48:23.0992453+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sitzt",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:48.5336776+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sitzt",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:20.8711822+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich saß",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:20:48.4140632+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du saßest",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:10:28.3920753+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er saß",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:35.2424992+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "siedzieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saßt",
    "ParentId": 145,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:25:55.5261484+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lese",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:09.8831141+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du liest",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:44:47.7083902+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er liest",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:26:20.1320022+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lest",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:10:15.672166+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich las",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:10:33.7760442+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lasest",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:44.5915752+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er las",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:39.5817573+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czytać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr last",
    "ParentId": 149,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:31.4151906+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich höre",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:31.613673+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hörst",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:02:13.2234754+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hört",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:45.0552086+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hört",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:19:16.0705285+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hörte",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:48.8875706+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hörtest",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:15:48.8399143+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hörte",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:15:03.4241605+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "słyszeć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hörtet",
    "ParentId": 153,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:56.2311056+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich merke",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:30.6714229+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du merkst",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:39.53509+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er merkt",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:45:29.7480941+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr merkt",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:19:47.070359+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich merkte",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:29.5206126+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du merktest",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:06.8620595+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er merkte",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:35:12.7080619+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zauważać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr merktet",
    "ParentId": 157,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:05:09.294389+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich reagiere",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:11:14.6735245+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du reagierst",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:44:57.9162927+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er reagiert",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:44:27.8284555+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr reagiert",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:29.6345948+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich reagierte",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:14:01.2404577+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du reagiertest",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:14:31.9363586+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er reagierte",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:41.9032334+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "reagować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr reagiertet",
    "ParentId": 161,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:16:55.8954601+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fliege",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:45:01.8282203+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fliegst",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:19:02.0386845+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fliegt",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:26:38.8198912+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fliegt",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:18:09.335021+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich flog",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:48:08.1711634+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du flogst",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:23:01.1272922+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er flog",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:26:17.7901064+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "latać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr flogt",
    "ParentId": 165,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:05:12.5023517+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich versuche",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:15:17.7119965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du versuchst",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:12:51.3848745+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er versucht",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:14:36.6483104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr versucht",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:38.6312881+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich versuchte",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:10.5119186+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du versuchtest",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:26:27.6919263+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er versuchte",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:14.0647289+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na v) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr versuchtet",
    "ParentId": 169,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:43.4184498+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sehe an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:53.290399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siehst an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:05.0238647+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sieht an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:45:25.3961905+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seht an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:40.3387383+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sah an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:18:58.0386722+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sahst an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:49.6423975+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sah an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:16:31.799508+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na a) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saht an",
    "ParentId": 173,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:02.3258377+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lande",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:18:22.5429051+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du landest",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:44:43.012275+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er landet",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:14:59.5553601+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr landet",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:03:04.3511842+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich landete",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:09:59.6406554+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du landetest",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:32:03.5571133+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er landete",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:17:55.7690949+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lądować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr landetet",
    "ParentId": 177,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:36.9276519+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich laufe los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:52.9829952+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du läufst los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:07.0315079+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er läuft los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:03:25.9190425+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lauft los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:26:10.003998+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lief los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:16.3548919+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du liefst los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:11:00.8898999+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lief los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:45.1271742+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać biec (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lieft los",
    "ParentId": 181,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:03.4243773+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich öffne",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:45:53.9480535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du öffnest",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:43:37.1887434+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er öffnet",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:11:26.9853521+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr öffnet",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:48.8085243+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich öffnete",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:44.0375713+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du öffnetest",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:01.5545263+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er öffnete",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T21:09:46.1512369+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "otwierać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr öffnetet",
    "ParentId": 185,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:19:23.4464392+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich glaube",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:26:35.2278269+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du glaubst",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:10:03.5602264+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er glaubt",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:56.080566+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr glaubt",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:19.2807325+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich glaubte",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:10:44.3281238+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du glaubtest",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:11.0874024+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er glaubte",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:14:13.3203007+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wierzyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr glaubtet",
    "ParentId": 189,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:21:52.6856093+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich übe",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:18:03.8309404+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du übst",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:02:21.5754346+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er übt",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:48.399262+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr übt",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:11:18.9374699+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich übte",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:47:49.5231111+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du übtest",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:43:25.8529818+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er übte",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:47:04.7154255+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ćwiczyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr übtet",
    "ParentId": 193,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:35.832568+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gucke",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:11:10.0174937+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du guckst",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:11:22.6893618+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er guckt",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:59.8394648+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr guckt",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:46.1144008+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich guckte",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:20:42.8780282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gucktest",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:10:20.0882368+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er guckte",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:16:39.111444+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gapić się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gucktet",
    "ParentId": 197,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:58.5909928+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fahre",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:51:17.8974048+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "8.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fährst",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:44:23.9004189+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fährt",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:12:18.7434863+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fahrt",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:45:50.7479849+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fuhr",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:18:17.7589189+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fuhrst",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:26:02.7965129+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fuhr",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:49:25.2585513+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fuhrt",
    "ParentId": 201,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:46:56.6035844+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rede",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:13:40.2806179+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du redest",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T21:11:56.4716697+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er redet",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:25.5700708+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr redet",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:20:38.5821137+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich redete",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:17:14.9273214+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du redetest",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:51:13.6165542+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er redete",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T22:47:56.7151482+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozmawiać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr redetet",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T20:10:52.8421345+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróż, wycieczka (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Reise",
    "ParentId": 162,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:46.4967124+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróż, wycieczka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Reisen",
    "ParentId": 162,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:53.8006949+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jednostka, jedność (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Einheit",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:27:35.1187079+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jednostka, jedność (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Einheiten",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:42.6407462+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "włos (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Haar",
    "ParentId": 170,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:50.9766871+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "włos (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Haare",
    "ParentId": 170,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:51:17.0805122+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bliskość, pobliże (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Nähe",
    "ParentId": 174,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:57.4486416+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zasada (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Prinzip",
    "ParentId": 178,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:51:06.5365993+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zasada (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Prinzipien",
    "ParentId": 178,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:01.9289967+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "korzyść, zaleta (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Vorteil",
    "ParentId": 182,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:49:52.9295091+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "korzyść, zaleta (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Vorteile",
    "ParentId": 182,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T16:50:28.3287668+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmiana (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Änderung",
    "ParentId": 186,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:23:24.1110903+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmiana (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Änderungen",
    "ParentId": 186,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:43:59.1516027+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjątek (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Ausnahme",
    "ParentId": 190,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:23.7283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjątek (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Ausnahmen",
    "ParentId": 190,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:59.7760996+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budowa, budynek (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Bau",
    "ParentId": 194,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:51:31.8642999+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "budowa, budynek (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Bauten",
    "ParentId": 194,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:37:06.7713366+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hobby (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Hobby",
    "ParentId": 198,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:43.1640613+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hobby (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Hobbys",
    "ParentId": 198,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:29.9402177+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "konflikt (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Konflikt",
    "ParentId": 202,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:04:46.3665679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "konflikt (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Konflikte",
    "ParentId": 202,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:20:34.2974068+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kierownictwo, zarząd (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Leitung",
    "ParentId": 206,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:22:48.3364577+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kierownictwo, zarząd (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Leitungen",
    "ParentId": 206,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:42:27.8640556+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chęć, ochota (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Lust",
    "ParentId": 210,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T00:04:50.9425501+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chęć, ochota (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Lüste",
    "ParentId": 210,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:51:08.4164164+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "większość (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Mehrheit",
    "ParentId": 214,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-30T23:46:58.3927722+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "większość (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Mehrheiten",
    "ParentId": 214,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:02.6173303+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "samochód (na A) (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Auto",
    "ParentId": 218,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:34.2937407+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "samochód (na A) (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Autos",
    "ParentId": 218,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:36:46.1341272+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziecko (na B) (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Baby",
    "ParentId": 222,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:21.4698578+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziecko (na B) (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Babys",
    "ParentId": 222,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:36:50.542094+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kino (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Kino",
    "ParentId": 226,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:38:18.9655293+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kino (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Kinos",
    "ParentId": 226,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:38:49.813282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "strajk (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Streik",
    "ParentId": 230,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:55.4297572+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "strajk (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Streiks",
    "ParentId": 230,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:18.1339052+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hotel (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Hotel",
    "ParentId": 234,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:38:04.2215915+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hotel (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Hotels",
    "ParentId": 234,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:38:06.9897081+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "park (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Park",
    "ParentId": 238,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:38:00.9016223+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "park (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Parks",
    "ParentId": 238,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:01.2299545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nauczyciel (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Lehrer",
    "ParentId": 242,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:36:23.1187789+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nauczyciel (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Lehrer",
    "ParentId": 242,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:38:14.1815555+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nauczycielka (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Lehrerin",
    "ParentId": 246,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:44.7337751+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nauczycielka (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Lehrerinnen",
    "ParentId": 246,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:30.837857+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "samochód (na W) (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Wagen",
    "ParentId": 250,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:37:48.4056064+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "samochód (na W) (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Wagen",
    "ParentId": 250,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:36:54.9181328+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wujek (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Onkel",
    "ParentId": 254,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-31T19:36:35.3101832+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wujek (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Onkel",
    "ParentId": 254,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:55.3879516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fresse",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:27:28.6387918+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du frisst",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:17:24.4505627+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er frisst",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:49.3782607+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fresst",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:17.0185155+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fraß",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9989959+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fraßest",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9990005+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fraß",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:23.9968671+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "żreć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fraßt",
    "ParentId": 209,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:41.311224+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich trinke",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:49.070066+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du trinkst",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:23:42.9030252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er trinkt",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:30:52.3654957+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr trinkt",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:46:47.6944548+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich trank",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:46.5380772+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du trankst",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:19:51.6015914+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er trank",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:04.82328+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr trankt",
    "ParentId": 213,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9990464+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bekomme",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:38:34.2654904+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bekommst",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9990557+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bekommt",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:03.2762743+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bekommt",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:17:59.3303099+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bekam",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:35:51.2117286+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bekamst",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:54.5858674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bekam",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:25:28.919567+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dostawać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bekamt",
    "ParentId": 217,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9990835+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich studiere",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:35:16.7079532+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du studierst",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:32:14.8210291+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er studiert",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9991485+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr studiert",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:18.4021847+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich studierte",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:46.0393648+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du studiertest",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:31:15.5335252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er studierte",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:35:59.9944324+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "studiować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr studiertet",
    "ParentId": 225,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9991721+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich arbeite",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.999177+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du arbeitest",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:09.6688428+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er arbeitet",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:47.7327766+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr arbeitet",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:15:26.666601+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich arbeitete",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:36:57.5072518+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du arbeitetest",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:59.1158888+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er arbeitete",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:28:36.0052039+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pracować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr arbeitetet",
    "ParentId": 229,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:08:14.1506393+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich warte",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:05.7451472+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wartest",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:51:21.8092232+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wartet",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:13.1643597+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wartet",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:14.737078+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wartete",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:49:51.3253518+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wartetest",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:35:53.7544934+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wartete",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:40.4161708+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czekać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wartetet",
    "ParentId": 233,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:22:08.1206957+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zeige",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:36:38.0434126+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du zeigst",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:10.1003886+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zeigt",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:52.3858676+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zeigt",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.99927+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zeigte",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:32:52.1248542+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zeigtest",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9992799+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zeigte",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:56.1945771+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na z) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zeigtet",
    "ParentId": 237,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:36:19.5463733+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verkaufe",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:39:44.7370904+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du verkaufst",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:27:58.8453665+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er verkauft",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:06.0283675+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verkauft",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:38.0447603+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verkaufte",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9993144+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du verkauftest",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:18:27.3370982+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er verkaufte",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:41:33.2565366+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sprzedawać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verkauftet",
    "ParentId": 241,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:33.5055008+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gehe weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:28:35.6543797+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gehst weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:32:37.7328992+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er geht weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:24.5699325+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr geht weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:25:04.5916607+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ging weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:24.0522577+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gingst weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:19.7990142+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er ging weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:36:11.651545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "iść dalej (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gingt weiter",
    "ParentId": 245,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.999372+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich helfe",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:45.0247095+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hilfst",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:14:19.9014025+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hilft",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:08.3364894+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr helft",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:17:54.3783703+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich half",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:25.1101552+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du halfst",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:28.5362728+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er half",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9994073+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pomagać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr halft",
    "ParentId": 249,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:37:44.6977864+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sehe um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:33:57.2364881+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siehst um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9994226+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sieht um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:53.0231287+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seht um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:36:09.0983622+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sah um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9994378+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sahst um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:38:41.4895264+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sah um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:05.2489641+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozglądać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saht um",
    "ParentId": 253,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:39:19.6012097+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich finde",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:07.7389049+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du findest",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:38:08.433626+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er findet",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:44:57.6711407+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr findet",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:44:34.3032965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fand",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:40.436141+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fandst",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:18:09.489039+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fand",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:27:07.1107875+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "znajdować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fandet",
    "ParentId": 257,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:20:18.3682063+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich probiere",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:46:25.0386553+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du probierst",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9995258+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er probiert",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:04.0189755+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr probiert",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:51:13.401392+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich probierte",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:26:03.542137+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du probiertest",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:13.5940919+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er probierte",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:31:20.1814016+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "próbować (na p) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr probiertet",
    "ParentId": 261,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:20:28.7693472+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich passe",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9995623+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du passt",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:11.4568649+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er passt",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9995751+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr passt",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:21.6808048+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich passte",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:46:44.1345037+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du passtest",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.999591+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er passte",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:37.8660736+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pasować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr passtet",
    "ParentId": 265,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9996015+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kaufe",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:24:29.7986687+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kaufst",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9996122+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kauft",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:15:20.6191865+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kauft",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:58.4645577+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kaufte",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:16:42.889542+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kauftest",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:43:45.7918575+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kaufte",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:43.5568175+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kupować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kauftet",
    "ParentId": 269,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:19:48.1136826+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lache",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:25:23.1194449+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lachst",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:28:48.6063083+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lacht",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:27.1137376+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lacht",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:37:12.251202+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lachte",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:20:25.5923794+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lachtest",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9997268+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lachte",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:38:26.6098337+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "śmiać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lachtet",
    "ParentId": 277,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:13.6316527+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zeige auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:49:39.7174695+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du zeigst auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:17.2189766+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zeigt auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:31:51.7732145+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zeigt auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:20:39.4973021+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zeigte auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:15:10.3633751+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zeigtest auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:28:06.0705493+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zeigte auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9997757+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pokazywać (na a) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zeigtet auf",
    "ParentId": 281,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:56.0707881+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich motiviere",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:35:43.1957491+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du motivierst",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9997921+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er motiviert",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9997976+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr motiviert",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:57.84143+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich motivierte",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:37:17.867225+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du motiviertest",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:30:57.9738348+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er motivierte",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.999822+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "motywować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr motiviertet",
    "ParentId": 285,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:27:48.5174811+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich laufe",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:07.3390393+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du läufst",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9998386+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er läuft",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:52.5809777+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lauft",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9998496+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lief",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:35.9299594+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du liefst",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:46:16.3267215+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lief",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:36:08.3716787+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "biegać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lieft",
    "ParentId": 289,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:26.5753825+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ziehe",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:17.8969492+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du ziehst",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:28.8501626+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zieht",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:24.1530574+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zieht",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:33.8101112+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zog",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9999+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zogst",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:10:44.2857588+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zog",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:49.0027045+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ciągnąć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zogt",
    "ParentId": 293,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:16:19.209725+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ziehe an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:16:58.3534696+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du ziehst an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:13.7787953+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zieht an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:50:46.8530634+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zieht an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:30:32.5257224+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zog an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:27.9999452+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zogst an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:36:05.70765+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zog an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:28.4819907+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ubierać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zogt an",
    "ParentId": 297,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:45.2300998+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ziehe aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:36:30.4502429+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du ziehst aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:40:31.2329009+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zieht aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:05.2829801+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zieht aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:42:19.9396421+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zog aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:05.4656333+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zogst aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:59.6940813+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zog aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:27.599252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rozbierać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zogt aus",
    "ParentId": 301,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:51:04.8049604+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gebe",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:55:20.824283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gibst",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:38:00.1309329+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er gibt",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:53:40.568662+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gebt",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:11.6330914+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gab",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:09:37.4941694+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gabst",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:40.1988972+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er gab",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:36:48.4274494+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dawać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gabt",
    "ParentId": 305,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:20.610088+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zahle",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:33:19.4846097+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du zahlst",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:10.3431063+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zahlt",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:39:13.6985111+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zahlt",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:50.775321+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zahlte",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:28:11.2466283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zahltest",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:18:09.4661854+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zahlte",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:27:41.3899989+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na z) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zahltet",
    "ParentId": 309,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:46.3160992+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bestelle",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0001094+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bestellst",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:24:33.9026282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bestellt",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:49.2601621+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bestellt",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:09.00913+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bestellte",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.000133+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bestelltest",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:31:06.5495708+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bestellte",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:17:12.5293909+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamawiać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bestelltet",
    "ParentId": 313,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:56.399346+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kenne",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:46:38.9026698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kennst",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:26:26.1500104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kennt",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:25:58.4712711+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kennt",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:24:53.271731+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kannte",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0001805+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kanntest",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:50:37.7970581+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kannte",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:35.2988094+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wiedzieć (na k) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kanntet",
    "ParentId": 317,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:21:21.1130957+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich mag",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0002045+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du magst",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:30:20.5497315+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er mag",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:32:17.6930916+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr mögt",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0002224+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich mochte",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:43.9761466+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du mochtest",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:44:20.5515142+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er mochte",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:23.250849+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "lubić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr mochtet",
    "ParentId": 321,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:10:37.213883+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bringe",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0002559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bringst",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:20:42.9692926+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bringt",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:06.2471005+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bringt",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:35:47.3638412+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich brachte",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0002801+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du brachtest",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:11:16.3495395+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er brachte",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:25:47.3113867+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przynosić (na b) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr brachtet",
    "ParentId": 325,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:14:43.1714545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich treffe",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:47.0801767+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du triffst",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0003107+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er trifft",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0003167+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr trefft",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:22:09.1355131+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich traf",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:27:10.7509702+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du trafst",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T03:10:23.9819178+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er traf",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:20:52.3612798+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "spotykać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr traft",
    "ParentId": 329,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:45:28.8789809+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich überlege",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:19:14.8818154+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du überlegst",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:15:45.4831385+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er überlegt",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:36:14.4344493+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr überlegt",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:38:22.3296964+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich überlegte",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0003788+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du überlegtest",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:17:19.3933547+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er überlegte",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:28:30.8864706+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na ü) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr überlegtet",
    "ParentId": 333,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:37:56.850932+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich atme",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:16:10.3629185+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du atmest",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:32.1511834+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er atmet",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:26:01.7912273+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr atmet",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:21:49.7836293+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich atmete",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:28:31.6931411+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du atmetest",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.000435+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er atmete",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0004431+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oddychać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr atmetet",
    "ParentId": 337,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:53:48.8806989+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich atme ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0004559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du atmest ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:39:13.4093764+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er atmet ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:34:52.0520733+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr atmet ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:40.7699709+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich atmete ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:18:03.1290684+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du atmetest ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:19:22.8657388+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er atmete ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:25:28.1982422+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wdychać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr atmetet ein",
    "ParentId": 341,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:32:22.1169522+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich läute",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-01T01:07:28.0005088+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du läutest",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:29:39.7740617+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er läutet",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:43:01.1358314+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr läutet",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:41:39.5285705+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich läutete",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:40:06.298183+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du läutetest",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:24:59.3744742+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er läutete",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T02:25:49.2702868+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (dzwonkiem) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr läutetet",
    "ParentId": 345,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-02T16:23:16.9203539+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rufe an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1660773+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du rufst an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1660874+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ruft an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1660975+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ruft an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661069+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rief an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661176+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du riefst an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166128+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er rief an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661383+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dzwonić (przez telefon) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr rieft an",
    "ParentId": 349,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661487+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erschrecke",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661586+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du erschreckst",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661682+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er erschreckt",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166178+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erschreckt",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661888+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erschreckte",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1661995+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du erschrecktest",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662098+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er erschreckte",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662204+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przestraszyć się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erschrecktet",
    "ParentId": 353,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662311+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sage",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662418+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du sagst",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662519+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sagt",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662616+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sagt",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166271+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sagte",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662815+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sagtest",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1662922+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sagte",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663027+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mówić (na sa) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sagtet",
    "ParentId": 357,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663133+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stelle vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663233+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stellst vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663336+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er stellt vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663439+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stellt vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663542+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stellte vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663649+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du stelltest vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663755+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stellte vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1663863+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przedstawiać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stelltet vor",
    "ParentId": 361,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166397+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ändere",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664075+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du änderst",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166418+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ändert",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664285+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ändert",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664389+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich änderte",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664489+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du ändertest",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664598+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er änderte",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664705+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na ä) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ändertet",
    "ParentId": 365,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664811+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dusche",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1664919+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du duschst",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166502+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er duscht",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665121+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr duscht",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665219+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich duschte",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665325+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du duschtest",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166544+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er duschte",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:53:17.2408044+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać prysznic (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr duschtet",
    "ParentId": 369,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665651+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fahre heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665757+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fährst heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665861+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fährt heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1665971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fahrt heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666078+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fuhr heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666198+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fuhrst heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666304+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fuhr heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166641+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jechać do domu (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fuhrt heim",
    "ParentId": 373,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich spiele",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666626+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du spielst",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166673+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er spielt",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666832+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr spielt",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1666937+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich spielte",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667084+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du spieltest",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667189+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er spielte",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166729+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "grać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr spieltet",
    "ParentId": 377,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667396+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sehe fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667503+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siehst fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667611+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sieht fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667717+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seht fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667825+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sah fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1667932+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sahst fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668039+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sah fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668146+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oglądać telewizję (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saht fern",
    "ParentId": 381,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668258+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich füge zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668371+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fügst zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668482+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fügt zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668589+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fügt zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668692+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fügte zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668799+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fügtest zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1668906+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fügte zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1669014+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zadawać (obrażenia) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fügtet zu",
    "ParentId": 385,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1669121+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stehe",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166924+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stehst",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1669347+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er steht",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1669453+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr steht",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166956+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stand",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1669671+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du standst",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.166978+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stand",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1669887+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "stać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr standet",
    "ParentId": 389,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1670001+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gebe zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1670118+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gibst zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1670231+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er gibt zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167034+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gebt zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1670444+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gab zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1670559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gabst zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167067+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er gab zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167078+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyznawać się (do błędu) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gabt zu",
    "ParentId": 393,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1670892+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hänge",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hängst",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671109+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hängt",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671213+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hängt",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671327+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hing",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671443+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hingst",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671557+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hing",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167167+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wieszać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hingt",
    "ParentId": 397,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671779+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich besuche",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1671889+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du besuchst",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er besucht",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672114+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr besucht",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672224+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich besuchte",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672337+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du besuchtest",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672449+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er besuchte",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odwiedzać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr besuchtet",
    "ParentId": 401,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672671+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wechsle",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672781+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wechselst",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672887+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wechselt",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1672994+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wechselt",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673106+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wechselte",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673234+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wechseltest",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167335+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wechselte",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673461+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na w) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wechseltet",
    "ParentId": 405,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673575+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich biete an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673686+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bietest an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673798+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bietet an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1673912+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bietet an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674025+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bot an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674142+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du botst an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674257+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bot an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674365+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "oferować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr botet an",
    "ParentId": 409,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167448+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schmecke",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674591+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schmeckst",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674703+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schmeckt",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674815+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schmeckt",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1674926+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schmeckte",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:42:07.659635+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schmecktest",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675158+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schmeckte",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675272+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "smakować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schmecktet",
    "ParentId": 413,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675386+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stelle",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675502+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stellst",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675614+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er stellt",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675729+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stellt",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675842+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stellte",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1675958+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du stelltest",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676075+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stellte",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676191+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ustawiać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stelltet",
    "ParentId": 417,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schneide",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676422+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schneidest",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676538+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schneidet",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676655+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schneidet",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167677+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schnitt",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1676889+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schnittest",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677045+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schnitt",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677159+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kroić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schnittet",
    "ParentId": 421,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677285+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kämpfe",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677401+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kämpfst",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677517+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kämpft",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677632+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kämpft",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167775+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kämpfte",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:51:05.4814117+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kämpftest",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1677988+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kämpfte",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678106+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "walczyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kämpftet",
    "ParentId": 425,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678225+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich töte",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678343+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du tötest",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678457+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er tötet",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.167857+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tötet",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tötete",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678799+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du tötetest",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1678917+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er tötete",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679037+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zabijać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tötetet",
    "ParentId": 429,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679156+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fange an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679276+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fängst an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679393+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fängt an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679508+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fangt an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679622+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fing an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679743+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fingst an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679864+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fing an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1679982+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na a) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fingt an",
    "ParentId": 433,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680099+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hole ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680215+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du holst ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680335+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er holt ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680452+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr holt ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680571+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich holte ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680692+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du holtest ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680814+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er holte ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1680933+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "odbierać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr holtet ab",
    "ParentId": 437,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681051+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich putze",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681168+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du putzt",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681286+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er putzt",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr putzt",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681527+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich putzte",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681646+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du putztest",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681761+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er putzte",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1681874+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czyścić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr putztet",
    "ParentId": 441,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682019+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gehe los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682143+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gehst los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682264+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er geht los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682369+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr geht los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682473+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ging los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682589+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gingst los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682709+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er ging los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zaczynać (na l) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gingt los",
    "ParentId": 445,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1682946+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich starte",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1683067+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du startest",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1683182+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er startet",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1683297+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr startet",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168342+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich startete",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1683545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du startetest",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168367+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er startete",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1683792+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "startować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr startetet",
    "ParentId": 449,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1683914+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich folge",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168404+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du folgst",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:49:56.449757+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er folgt",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168428+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr folgt",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1684399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich folgte",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1684524+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du folgtest",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1684649+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er folgte",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1684773+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podążać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr folgtet",
    "ParentId": 453,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1684895+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich biege ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685021+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du biegst ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685146+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er biegt ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685269+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr biegt ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685393+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bog ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bogst ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685641+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bog ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685781+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "skręcać (w ulicę) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bogt ab",
    "ParentId": 457,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1685904+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hüpfe",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686031+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hüpfst",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686156+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hüpft",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hüpft",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686408+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hüpfte",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hüpftest",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686659+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hüpfte",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podskakiwać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hüpftet",
    "ParentId": 461,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1686909+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich klaue",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1687068+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du klaust",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1687192+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er klaut",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1687315+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr klaut",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168744+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich klaute",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1687569+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du klautest",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1687697+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er klaute",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1687823+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na k) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr klautet",
    "ParentId": 465,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:12.2975743+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich untersuche",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688074+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du untersuchst",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.16882+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er untersucht",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688328+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr untersucht",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688457+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich untersuchte",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688586+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du untersuchtest",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688715+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er untersuchte",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688842+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "badać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr untersuchtet",
    "ParentId": 469,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1688971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zerstöre",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1689096+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du zerstörst",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.168922+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zerstört",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1689346+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zerstört",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1689475+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zerstörte",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1689607+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zerstörtest",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1689738+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zerstörte",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:22.3377698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "niszczyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zerstörtet",
    "ParentId": 473,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1689997+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich suche",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690128+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du suchst",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690271+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sucht",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sucht",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690529+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich suchte",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690658+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du suchtest",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er suchte",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1690916+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szukać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr suchtet",
    "ParentId": 477,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691044+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verliere",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691169+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du verlierst",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691296+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er verliert",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691424+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verliert",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691554+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verlor",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691685+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du verlorst",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691817+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er verlor",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1691947+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przegrywać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verlort",
    "ParentId": 481,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.169208+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schiebe",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1692214+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schiebst",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1692345+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schiebt",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1692477+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schiebt",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1692608+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schob",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1692742+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schobst",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:48:04.6825778+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schob",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1692995+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pchać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schobt",
    "ParentId": 485,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693126+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schließe",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693261+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schließt",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693394+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schließt",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693527+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schließt",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693656+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schloss",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693791+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schlossest",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1693923+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schloss",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694056+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schlosst",
    "ParentId": 489,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.169419+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schließe zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694324+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schließt zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694458+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schließt zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694586+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schließt zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694715+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schloss zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694849+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schlossest zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1694996+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schloss zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1695131+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamykać (na klucz) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schlosst zu",
    "ParentId": 493,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1695267+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schaue",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1695398+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schaust",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1695532+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schaut",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1695665+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schaut",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.16958+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schaute",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1695943+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schautest",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696095+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schaute",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696254+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "patrzeć (na s) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schautet",
    "ParentId": 497,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696391+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich passiere",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696525+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du passierst",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696655+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er passiert",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr passiert",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1696921+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich passierte",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.169709+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du passiertest",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:49:44.5938426+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er passierte",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1697363+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zdarzać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr passiertet",
    "ParentId": 501,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1697496+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich seufze",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1697634+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du seufzt",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1697771+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er seufzt",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1697908+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seufzt",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698043+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich seufzte",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.169818+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du seufztest",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698316+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er seufzte",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698453+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wzdychać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seufztet",
    "ParentId": 505,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698587+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich passe auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698722+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du passt auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698857+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er passt auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1698995+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr passt auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1699132+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich passte auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1699272+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du passtest auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1699407+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er passte auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1699543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uważać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr passtet auf",
    "ParentId": 509,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1699682+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erkläre",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.169983+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du erklärst",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1699965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er erklärt",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1700104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erklärt",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170024+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erklärte",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1700376+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du erklärtest",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1700514+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er erklärte",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1700653+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyjaśniać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erklärtet",
    "ParentId": 513,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1700792+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich flüstere",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1700933+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du flüsterst",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1701069+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er flüstert",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1701209+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr flüstert",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1701349+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich flüsterte",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170149+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du flüstertest",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1701628+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er flüsterte",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170177+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "szeptać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr flüstertet",
    "ParentId": 517,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1701906+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bleibe",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702048+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bleibst",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702185+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bleibt",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702317+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bleibt",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702453+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich blieb",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702595+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bliebst",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702736+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er blieb",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1702876+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (w domu) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bliebt",
    "ParentId": 521,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1703014+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gewöhne mich",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1703157+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gewöhnst dich",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1703297+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er gewöhnt sich",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170344+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gewöhnt euch",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1703582+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gewöhnte mich",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1703724+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gewöhntest dich",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1703866+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er gewöhnte sich",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1704009+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przyzwyczajać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gewöhntet euch",
    "ParentId": 525,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1704148+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich werde",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1704285+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wirst",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170442+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wird",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1704566+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr werdet",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1704714+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wurde",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170486+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wurdest",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705004+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wurde",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.170514+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawać (lekarzem) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wurdet",
    "ParentId": 529,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705277+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tue",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705415+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du tust",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705556+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er tut",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705694+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tut",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705831+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tat",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1705976+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du tatst",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706119+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er tat",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706258+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić (na t) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tatet",
    "ParentId": 533,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fühle",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fühlst",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706685+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fühlt",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706824+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fühlt",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1706965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fühlte",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707144+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fühltest",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707284+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fühlte",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707427+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czuć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fühltet",
    "ParentId": 537,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707568+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich klappe",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707715+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du klappst",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707849+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er klappt",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1707994+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr klappt",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1708143+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich klappte",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1708293+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du klapptest",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1708432+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er klappte",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1708571+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "udawać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr klapptet",
    "ParentId": 541,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1708716+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich reise",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1708861+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du reist",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709004+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er reist",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709148+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr reist",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709291+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich reiste",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709439+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du reistest",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709585+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er reiste",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709738+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podróżować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr reistet",
    "ParentId": 545,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1709885+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stimme",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710033+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stimmst",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710166+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er stimmt",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710306+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stimmt",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710449+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stimmte",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710601+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du stimmtest",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710745+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stimmte",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1710894+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zgadzać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stimmtet",
    "ParentId": 549,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1711044+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich koche",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1711189+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kochst",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1711342+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kocht",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1711494+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kocht",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1711639+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kochte",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.171179+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kochtest",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1711937+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kochte",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1712087+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "gotować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kochtet",
    "ParentId": 553,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1712236+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sehe aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1712383+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siehst aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1712526+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sieht aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:48:53.4899841+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seht aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1712817+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sah aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1712969+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sahst aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1713122+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sah aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1713274+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wyglądać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saht aus",
    "ParentId": 557,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1713421+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fehle",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:52:59.5050282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fehlst",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1713713+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fehlt",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1713861+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fehlt",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714006+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fehlte",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714155+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fehltest",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714303+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fehlte",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714448+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brakować, dolegać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fehltet",
    "ParentId": 561,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714595+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich atme aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714745+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du atmest aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1714901+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er atmet aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1715051+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr atmet aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.17152+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich atmete aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1715349+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du atmetest aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1715496+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er atmete aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1715645+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wydychać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr atmetet aus",
    "ParentId": 565,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1715796+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dauere",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1715945+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du dauerst",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1716111+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er dauert",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.171629+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dauert",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1716456+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dauerte",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1716602+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du dauertest",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.171675+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er dauerte",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1716898+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trwać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dauertet",
    "ParentId": 569,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1717088+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lasse",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1717241+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lässt",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1717394+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lässt",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1717545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lasst",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1717696+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ließ",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1717851+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du ließest",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718001+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er ließ",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718151+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zostawiać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ließt",
    "ParentId": 573,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718297+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erzähle",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718446+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du erzählst",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718597+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er erzählt",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718744+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erzählt",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1718895+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erzählte",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719049+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du erzähltest",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719205+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er erzählte",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719357+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opowiadać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erzähltet",
    "ParentId": 577,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erinnere mich",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719677+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du erinnerst dich",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719826+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er erinnert sich",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1719977+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erinnert euch",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1720127+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erinnerte mich",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1720284+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du erinnertest dich",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1720448+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er erinnerte sich",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.17206+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pamiętać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erinnertet euch",
    "ParentId": 581,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1720756+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bade",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1720912+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du badest",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1721071+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er badet",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.172123+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr badet",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1721388+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich badete",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1721546+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du badetest",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1721702+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er badete",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1721856+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kąpać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr badetet",
    "ParentId": 585,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1722011+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gefalle",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1722166+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gefällst",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:53:26.8807912+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er gefällt",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1722467+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gefallt",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1722619+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gefiel",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1722776+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gefielst",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.172293+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er gefiel",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1723087+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podobać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gefielt",
    "ParentId": 589,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1723244+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich diene",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1723399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du dienst",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1723555+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er dient",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1723709+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dient",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1723863+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich diente",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.172402+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du dientest",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1724183+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er diente",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1724344+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "służyć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dientet",
    "ParentId": 593,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1724498+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bezahle",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1724654+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bezahlst",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1724805+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bezahlt",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1724964+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bezahlt",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1725122+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bezahlte",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.172528+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bezahltest",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1725439+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bezahlte",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1725597+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "płacić (na b) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bezahltet",
    "ParentId": 597,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.172576+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich scheine",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1725928+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du scheinst",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:41:08.2600106+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er scheint",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1726238+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr scheint",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1726399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schien",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1726563+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schienst",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1726727+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schien",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1726891+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świecić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schient",
    "ParentId": 601,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1727092+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bereite vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1727249+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bereitest vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:55:17.7845184+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bereitet vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1727559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bereitet vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1727717+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bereitete vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1727882+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bereitetest vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1728047+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bereitete vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1728211+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "przygotowywać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bereitetet vor",
    "ParentId": 605,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1728369+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich parke",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1728528+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du parkst",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.172868+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er parkt",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1728838+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr parkt",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1728994+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich parkte",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1729154+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du parktest",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1729314+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er parkte",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1729471+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parkować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr parktet",
    "ParentId": 609,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1729636+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich beobachte",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1729802+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du beobachtest",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1729959+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er beobachtet",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1730111+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr beobachtet",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1730268+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich beobachtete",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.173043+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du beobachtetest",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1730589+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er beobachtete",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1730749+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obserwować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr beobachtetet",
    "ParentId": 613,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1730908+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verändere mich",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1731074+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du veränderst dich",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1731237+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er verändert sich",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1731394+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verändert euch",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1731559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich veränderte mich",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1731718+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du verändertest dich",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1731884+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er veränderte sich",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1732048+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zmieniać (na v) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verändertet euch",
    "ParentId": 617,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1732211+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rieche",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1732371+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du riechst",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1732533+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er riecht",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1732698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr riecht",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1732865+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich roch",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1733028+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du rochst",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1733189+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er roch",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1733358+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pachnieć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr rocht",
    "ParentId": 621,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1733524+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wasche",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.173369+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wäschst",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1733853+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wäscht",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1734014+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wascht",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1734182+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wusch",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:41:20.8118418+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wuschest",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1734511+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wusch",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1734674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "myć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wuscht",
    "ParentId": 625,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1734836+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich investiere",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735001+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du investierst",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735156+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er investiert",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735316+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr investiert",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735477+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich investierte",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735641+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du investiertest",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735799+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er investierte",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1735964+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "inwestować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr investiertet",
    "ParentId": 629,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich koste",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736238+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kostest",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736362+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kostet",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736495+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kostet",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736624+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kostete",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736761+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kostetest",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1736897+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kostete",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.173707+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kosztować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kostetet",
    "ParentId": 633,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1737217+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich vergesse",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1737355+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du vergisst",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1737492+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er vergisst",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1737629+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr vergesst",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1737767+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich vergaß",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1737907+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du vergaßest",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1738045+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er vergaß",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1738182+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapominać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr vergaßt",
    "ParentId": 637,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.173832+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verdiene",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1738462+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du verdienst",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1738598+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er verdient",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1738736+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verdient",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1738875+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verdiente",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739016+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du verdientest",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739153+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er verdiente",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739293+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zarabiać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verdientet",
    "ParentId": 641,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739431+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich meine",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739572+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du meinst",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.173971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er meint",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739849+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr meint",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1739986+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich meinte",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1740128+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du meintest",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1740269+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er meinte",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1740409+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć na myśli (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr meintet",
    "ParentId": 645,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1740548+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich füttere",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174069+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fütterst",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1740829+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er füttert",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1740971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr füttert",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174111+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fütterte",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1741252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du füttertest",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174139+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fütterte",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1741528+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "karmić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr füttertet",
    "ParentId": 649,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1741672+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bügle",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1741814+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bügelst",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1741954+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bügelt",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1742096+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bügelt",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1742252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bügelte",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1742392+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bügeltest",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1742531+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bügelte",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1742672+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "prasować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bügeltet",
    "ParentId": 653,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:50:39.1936147+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fege",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1742963+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fegst",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1743109+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fegt",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174326+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fegt",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1743403+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fegte",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1743567+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fegtest",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1743736+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fegte",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1743893+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zamiatać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fegtet",
    "ParentId": 657,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744049+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich trainiere",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744196+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du trainierst",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744346+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er trainiert",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744493+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr trainiert",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744644+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich trainierte",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744795+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du trainiertest",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1744952+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er trainierte",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1745104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "trenować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr trainiertet",
    "ParentId": 661,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1745264+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich streite",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du streitest",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1745591+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er streitet",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174574+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr streitet",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174588+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stritt",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1746056+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du strittest",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1746239+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stritt",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1746399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kłócić się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr strittet",
    "ParentId": 665,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1746555+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich flirte",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1746707+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du flirtest",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1746863+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er flirtet",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747052+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr flirtet",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747194+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich flirtete",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747356+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du flirtetest",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747505+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er flirtete",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747681+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "flirtować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr flirtetet",
    "ParentId": 669,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747845+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lade ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1747998+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lädst ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1748149+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lädt ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1748295+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ladet ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1748436+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lud ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1748592+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du ludst ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1748753+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lud ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.174892+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapraszać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ludet ein",
    "ParentId": 673,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1749089+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wähle",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1749249+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wählst",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1749405+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wählt",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1749558+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wählt",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1749709+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wählte",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1749861+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wähltest",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1750018+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wählte",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1750174+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wybierać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wähltet",
    "ParentId": 677,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1750328+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hoffe",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1750492+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hoffst",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1750664+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hofft",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:48:57.9301407+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hofft",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1751013+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hoffte",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1751192+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hofftest",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1751377+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hoffte",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1751543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mieć nadzieję (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hofftet",
    "ParentId": 681,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1751712+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bediene",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1751887+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bedienst",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1752074+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bedient",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1752252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bedient",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:44:56.2269198+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bediente",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1752622+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bedientest",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1752805+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bediente",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1752979+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "obsługiwać (klientów) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bedientet",
    "ParentId": 685,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1753153+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tanke",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1753321+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du tankst",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1753511+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er tankt",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1753687+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tankt",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1753852+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tankte",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1754034+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du tanktest",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1754208+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er tankte",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1754376+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tankować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tanktet",
    "ParentId": 689,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1754543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich unterschreibe",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1754706+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du unterschreibst",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.175487+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er unterschreibt",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1755034+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr unterschreibt",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1755198+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich unterschrieb",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1755369+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du unterschriebst",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1755533+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er unterschrieb",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.175569+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "podpisywać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr unterschriebt",
    "ParentId": 693,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1755862+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich benutze",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1756023+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du benutzt",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1756178+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er benutzt",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1756341+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr benutzt",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1756503+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich benutzte",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1756669+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du benutztest",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1756842+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er benutzte",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1757057+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "używać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr benutztet",
    "ParentId": 697,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1757236+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich telefoniere",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1757399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du telefonierst",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1757563+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er telefoniert",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1757726+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr telefoniert",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1757894+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich telefonierte",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:55:41.8162357+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du telefoniertest",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1758251+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er telefonierte",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1758424+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telefonować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr telefoniertet",
    "ParentId": 701,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1758592+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich danke",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.175876+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du dankst",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.175892+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er dankt",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1759081+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dankt",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1759255+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dankte",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1759435+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du danktest",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1759624+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er dankte",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1759804+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dziękować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr danktet",
    "ParentId": 705,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1759973+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich feiere",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1760144+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du feierst",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1760321+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er feiert",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1760488+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr feiert",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1760661+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich feierte",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1760842+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du feiertest",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1761016+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er feierte",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1761198+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "świętować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr feiertet",
    "ParentId": 709,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1761367+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zünde an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1761542+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du zündest an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1761713+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er zündet an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1761883+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zündet an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1762057+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich zündete an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:40:49.1880972+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du zündetest an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1762418+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er zündete an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1762604+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zapalać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr zündetet an",
    "ParentId": 713,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1762783+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kaufe ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1762962+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kaufst ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1763132+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kauft ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:43:59.0514934+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kauft ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1763469+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kaufte ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1763647+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kauftest ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1763824+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kaufte ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1764002+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "robić zakupy (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kauftet ein",
    "ParentId": 717,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1764177+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich reserviere",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1764352+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du reservierst",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1764525+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er reserviert",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1764698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr reserviert",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1764872+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich reservierte",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1765056+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du reserviertest",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1765238+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er reservierte",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1765411+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "rezerwować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr reserviertet",
    "ParentId": 721,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1765593+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich plane",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1765786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du planst",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.176597+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er plant",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1766144+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr plant",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1766312+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich plante",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.176649+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du plantest",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1766663+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er plante",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1766838+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "planować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr plantet",
    "ParentId": 725,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1767059+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich behalte",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:53:09.7689264+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du behältst",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1767413+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er behält",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1767593+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr behaltet",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1767766+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich behielt",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1767941+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du behieltst",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1768124+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er behielt",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1768308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zatrzymywać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr behieltet",
    "ParentId": 729,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1768484+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich freue mich",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1768656+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du freust dich",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.176883+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er freut sich",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1769015+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr freut euch",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1769186+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich freute mich",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1769373+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du freutest dich",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1769548+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er freute sich",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1769723+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cieszyć się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr freutet euch",
    "ParentId": 733,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.17699+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kümmere mich",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1770074+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kümmerst dich",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1770253+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kümmert sich",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1770424+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kümmert euch",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1770579+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kümmerte mich",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1770759+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kümmertest dich",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1770945+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kümmerte sich",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1771134+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "opiekować się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kümmertet euch",
    "ParentId": 737,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.177132+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tausche",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1771502+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du tauschst",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1771678+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er tauscht",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.177185+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tauscht",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1772043+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tauschte",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1772237+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du tauschtest",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.177242+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er tauschte",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1772604+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "wymieniać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tauschtet",
    "ParentId": 741,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1772788+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ärgere mich",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1772974+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du ärgerst dich",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.177315+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ärgert sich",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1773323+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ärgert euch",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1773504+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ärgerte mich",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1773691+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du ärgertest dich",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1773864+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er ärgerte sich",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1774038+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "denerwować się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ärgertet euch",
    "ParentId": 745,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1774223+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich heirate",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1774405+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du heiratest",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1774584+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er heiratet",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1774762+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr heiratet",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1774945+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich heiratete",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1775125+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du heiratetest",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1775308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er heiratete",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1775493+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brać ślub (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr heiratetet",
    "ParentId": 749,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1775675+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wiederhole",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:44:08.4751449+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wiederholst",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1776013+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wiederholt",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1776192+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wiederholt",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1776372+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wiederholte",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1776559+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wiederholtest",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1776745+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wiederholte",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1776933+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "powtarzać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wiederholtet",
    "ParentId": 753,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1777159+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wachse auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1777341+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wächst auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.177752+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wächst auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1777705+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wachst auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1777886+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wuchs auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1778077+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wuchsest auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1778269+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wuchs auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1778467+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "dorastać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wuchst auf",
    "ParentId": 757,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1778657+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rette",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.177885+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du rettest",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1779027+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er rettet",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1779196+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr rettet",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1779379+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rettete",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1779577+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du rettetest",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1779764+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er rettete",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1779953+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ratować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr rettetet",
    "ParentId": 761,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1780134+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schütze",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1780316+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schützt",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1780497+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schützt",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1780679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schützt",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1780858+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schützte",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1781055+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schütztest",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1781246+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schützte",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1781441+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "chronić (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schütztet",
    "ParentId": 765,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1781635+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gehöre",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1781813+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gehörst",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1781986+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er gehört",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1782168+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gehört",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1782352+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gehörte",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.178255+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gehörtest",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1782741+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er gehörte",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1782929+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "należeć (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gehörtet",
    "ParentId": 769,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1783116+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich denke nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1783308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du denkst nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1783485+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er denkt nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1783662+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr denkt nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1783846+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dachte nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1784032+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du dachtest nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1784221+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er dachte nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1784413+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "zastanawiać się (na n) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dachtet nach",
    "ParentId": 773,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1784607+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erlebe",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1784791+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du erlebst",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1784982+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er erlebt",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:55:29.6323022+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erlebt",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1785365+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich erlebte",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1785576+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du erlebtest",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-04T21:41:49.7716947+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er erlebte",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1785967+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "doświadczać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr erlebtet",
    "ParentId": 777,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1786185+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich akzeptiere",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1786396+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du akzeptierst",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1786586+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er akzeptiert",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1786772+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr akzeptiert",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1786958+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich akzeptierte",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1787194+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du akzeptiertest",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1787391+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er akzeptierte",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1787584+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "akceptować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr akzeptiertet",
    "ParentId": 781,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1787777+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich begrenze",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1787965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du begrenzt",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1788154+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er begrenzt",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1788339+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr begrenzt",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1788528+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich begrenzte",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1788729+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du begrenztest",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1788927+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er begrenzte",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1789127+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ograniczać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr begrenztet",
    "ParentId": 785,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1789332+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich genieße",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1789525+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du genießt",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1789705+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er genießt",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1789889+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr genießt",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1790078+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich genoss",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1790281+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du genossest",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1790478+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er genoss",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1790675+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "czerpać przyjemność (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr genosst",
    "ParentId": 789,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1790867+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lächle",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1791057+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lächelst",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1791228+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lächelt",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1791399+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lächelt",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1791569+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lächelte",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1791766+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lächeltest",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.179194+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lächelte",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1792146+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "uśmiechać się (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lächeltet",
    "ParentId": 793,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1792356+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kopiere",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.179257+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kopierst",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.179278+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kopiert",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.179299+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kopiert",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1793179+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kopierte",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1793365+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kopiertest",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1793545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kopierte",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1793732+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kopiować (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kopiertet",
    "ParentId": 797,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1793905+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich nenne",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1794104+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du nennst",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1794309+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er nennt",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1794511+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr nennt",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.17947+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich nannte",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1794868+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du nanntest",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1795036+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er nannte",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1795208+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "nazywać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr nanntet",
    "ParentId": 801,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1795377+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schreibe",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1795548+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schreibst",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1795713+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schreibt",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1795879+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schreibt",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1796051+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schrieb",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1796224+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schriebst",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1796411+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schrieb",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1796586+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "pisać (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schriebt",
    "ParentId": 805,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.179676+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stehle",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1796935+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stiehlst",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1797151+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er stiehlt",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1797329+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stehlt",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1797808+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stahl",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1798009+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du stahlst",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1798188+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stahl",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1798365+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kraść (na s) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr stahlt",
    "ParentId": 809,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-04-03T21:23:25.1798543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  }
]